ronenbekerman.com 2017-09-01

# Privacy Policy - 3D Architectural Visualization & Rendering Blog

## 3\. USE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION

### 3.1. WHAT DOES COMPANY DO WITH COLLECTED INFORMATION?

 **(a) PERSONAL INFORMATION.** We will not share your personal information with any third parties without your consent, except as necessary to provide you with the services offered by us or to comply with the law. We will use your information as a greater collection of data related to the site in traffic discussions in articles posted on the blog. No individual users visit, whether you or another visitor, are discussed. The aggregate data is used for education purposes only and no reader of the article will be able to identify you.

 **(b) ANONYMOUS INFORMATION.** We use anonymous information to analyze our Site traffic. In addition, we may use anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis.

 **(c) USE OF COOKIES.** We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests or for other purposes. Promotions or advertisements displayed on our site may contain cookies. We do not have access to or control over information collected by outside advertisers on our site.

 **(d) DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION.** We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Company or its parent company, subsidiaries or affiliates, (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Company or the users of the Site, or (3) act under exigent circumstances to protect the safety of the public or users of the Site.

 **(e) SALE OF INFORMATION.** In order to accommodate changes in our business, we may sell or buy portions of our company or other companies or assets, including the information collected through this Web site. If Company or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the assets transferred to the acquirer.

 **(f) ACCESS TO INFORMATION.** Unfortunately, we do not maintain any procedures for you to review or request changes to the information that we collect about you, except that you may request that we remove all information about you from our database by contacting us in accordance with Section 6.1 below.
